<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on CTK</title>
    <link>/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on CTK</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 Diwali Celebration</title>
      <link>/events/2023_deepavali/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2023_deepavali/</guid>
      <description>Join us for a Glorious Diwali Celebration!
Date: 11.11.2023
Time: 10:30 AM onwards
Venue: Raderbergerstr. 205, 50968 Cologne.
Dear Friends and Community Members,
The festive season is upon us, and Cologne Tamil Kuzhumam is thrilled to invite you to our grand Diwali Celebration!
What to Expect:
Dazzling Decorations: Immerse yourself in the vibrant colors and enchanting decorations that will adorn our venue, creating a festive atmosphere like no other.
Cultural Extravaganza: Enjoy captivating cultural performances, traditional music, dance, and more that showcase the beauty of the Diwali traditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Vilambi celebrations</title>
      <link>/events/2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2018/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends and Community Members,
The dawn of a new year brings with it the promise of fresh beginnings, renewed hope, and the opportunity to celebrate the rich traditions of our Tamil culture. We are delighted to invite you to join us in welcoming the Tamil New Year with open hearts and joyous festivities.
What to Expect:
**Traditional Puthandu Decorations: Immerse yourself in the vibrant colors and traditional decorations that will adorn our venue, creating an atmosphere filled with Tamil heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Vihari celebrations</title>
      <link>/events/2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2019/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends and Community Members,
As the Tamil New Year approaches, we are excited to share a glimpse of the festivities that await us at our upcoming celebration. Join us as we usher in the New Year with joy, traditions, and cultural richness.
What to Expect:
Traditional Puthandu Decorations: Immerse yourself in the vibrant colors and traditional decorations that will adorn our venue, creating an atmosphere filled with Tamil heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023 Sobakiruthu celebrations</title>
      <link>/events/2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/2023/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends and Community Members,
As we approach the dawn of a new year, we are thrilled to announce our eagerly awaited Tamil New Year celebration for 2023. Join us in welcoming the year with joy, tradition, and the vibrant spirit of our Tamil culture.
What to Expect:
Traditional Puthandu Decorations: Immerse yourself in the vibrant colors and traditional decorations that will adorn our venue, creating an atmosphere filled with Tamil heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
